{
    "chunk-121ec3ad48d50acc94dd7a31f331140e": null,
    "chunk-22376ad0f4b05f5f20412a982321c613": [
        {
            "entity_name": "Carreras et al. (CoNLL 2002)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Carreras et al. won the CoNLL 2002 competition using binary AdaBoost classifiers and achieved high F-scores on Spanish and Dutch CoNLL 2002 datasets.",
            "source_entities": [
                "CARRERAS ET AL.",
                "CONLL 2002"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Li et al. (CoNLL 2003)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Li et al. implemented an SVM model on the CoNLL 2003 dataset and CMU seminar documents, achieving an 88.3% F score on the English CoNLL 2003 data.",
            "source_entities": [
                "LI ET AL.",
                "CONLL 2003"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Takeuchi and Collier (MUC6)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Takeuchi and Collier used SVM with various features on the MUC6 data and decided the final tag by voting of multiple one-vs-one SVM outputs.",
            "source_entities": [
                "TAKEUCHI AND COLLIER",
                "MUC6"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Segura Bedmar et al. (DrugNER)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Segura Bedmar et al. achieved state-of-the-art results in DrugNER by using a CRF with features like lexicon resources and word embeddings.",
            "source_entities": [
                "SEGURA BEDMAR ET AL.",
                "DRUGNER"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Liu et al. (DrugNER)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Liu et al. achieved state-of-the-art results in DrugNER by using a CRF with features like lexicon resources and word embeddings.",
            "source_entities": [
                "LIU ET AL.",
                "DRUGNER"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Rocktäschel et al. (DrugNER)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Rocktäschel et al. used a CRF with features constructed from dictionaries, ontologies, and prefixes-suffixes from chemical entities for the DrugNER task.",
            "source_entities": [
                "ROCKTÄSCHEL ET AL.",
                "DRUGNER"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Collobert and Weston",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Collobert and Weston proposed one of the first neural network architectures for NER, later replaced manually constructed feature vectors with word embeddings.",
            "source_entities": [
                "COLLOBERT AND WESTON",
                "COLLOBERT ET AL."
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Jochem (Hettne et al.)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Jochem, along with Hettne et al., is associated with lexicon resources used in the DrugNER task.",
            "source_entities": [
                "JOCHEM",
                "HETTNE ET AL."
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN) are used in word-level architectures for NER, with each word represented by its word embedding.",
            "source_entities": [
                "RECURRENT NEURAL NETWORKS",
                "BI-LSTM"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "chunk-ae2df4ba0c6d1016722d83ce8d5a38ab": null,
    "chunk-7fb7bd65b722433093ae9f1c85b9fe4e": [
        {
            "entity_name": "Lample et al.",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Lample et al. introduced a model architecture that achieved high F scores on multiple language NER datasets from CoNLL 2002 and 2003.",
            "source_entities": [
                "LAMPLE ET AL.",
                "LAMPLE ET AL. (2016)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Santos and Guimaraes",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Santos and Guimaraes implemented a model that achieved high F scores on Spanish CoNLL 2002 data and Portuguese NER data.",
            "source_entities": [
                "SANTOS AND GUIMARAES",
                "SANTOS AND CARDOSO"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "NeuroNER",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "NeuroNER is a toolkit for named entity recognition models, integrated with the BRAT annotation tool for ease of development, and achieved a high F score on the English CoNLL 2003 data.",
            "source_entities": [
                "NEURONER",
                "BRAT ANNOTATION TOOL",
                "ENGLISH CONLL 2003 DATA"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "GRU (Gated Recurrent Unit)",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "GRU is a type of RNN cell used by Yang et al. for word representation in their multi-task and multi-lingual joint learning system.",
            "source_entities": [
                "GRU (GATED RECURRENT UNIT)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "LSTM-B",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "LSTM-B stands for Long Short-Term Memory model with a backward look, used in NER architectures.",
            "source_entities": [
                "LSTM-B"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "LSTM-F",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "LSTM-F stands for Long Short-Term Memory model with a forward look, used in NER architectures.",
            "source_entities": [
                "LSTM-F"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "CRF",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "CRF refers to Conditional Random Fields, a model used in various NER systems for predicting entity labels.",
            "source_entities": [
                "CRF"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "chunk-cf36c8fd2948cda996a7b1897c0e732d": [
        {
            "entity_name": "CoNLL 2002 and 2003",
            "entity_type": "EVENT",
            "description": "CoNLL 2002 and 2003 are events where named entity recognition systems were evaluated on Spanish, Dutch, English, and German datasets.",
            "source_entities": [
                "CONLL 2002",
                "CONLL 2003"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "DrugNER",
            "entity_type": "EVENT",
            "description": "DrugNER is the event from SemEval 2013 task 9 where named entity recognition systems were evaluated on the dataset provided by DrugNER organization.",
            "source_entities": [
                "SEMEVAL 2013 TASK 9",
                "DRUGNER"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "MedLine and DrugBank",
            "entity_type": "GEO",
            "description": "MedLine and DrugBank are geo-locations where test data for the DrugNER dataset was collected.",
            "source_entities": [
                "MEDLINE",
                "DRUGBANK"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Agerri and Rigau",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Agerri and Rigau, also known as Rodrigo Agerri and German Rigau, are authors who presented a feature-engineered system for Spanish and German named entity recognition in 2016.",
            "source_entities": [
                "AGERRI AND RIGAU",
                "GERMAN RIGAU"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "CoNLL Datasets",
            "entity_type": "EVENT",
            "description": "CoNLL Datasets refer to the collections of data used for evaluating named entity recognition systems in various languages during the CoNLL events.",
            "source_entities": [
                "CONLL DATASETS"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "Language Datasets in CoNLL",
            "entity_type": "GEO",
            "description": "Spanish, Dutch, English, and German refer to the language datasets used in the CoNLL events for named entity recognition tasks.",
            "source_entities": [
                "SPANISH",
                "DUTCH",
                "ENGLISH",
                "GERMAN"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "chunk-156ddcb40418496642879b6eb85a5b26": []
}