{
    "image_1": [
        {
            "entity_name": "ELDERLY MAN WITH SUNGLASSES",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Elderly Man with Sunglasses是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'PERSON'相关联，后者是图像中识别出的一般人物实体。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "ELDERLY MAN WITH SUNGLASSES"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "PERSON"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "ELDERLY WOMAN IN BLACK JACKET",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Elderly Woman in Black Jacket是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'PERSON'相关联，后者是图像中识别出的一般人物实体。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "ELDERLY WOMAN IN BLACK JACKET"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "PERSON"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "WOMAN IN BLUE SUIT",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Woman in Blue Suit是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'PERSON'相关联，后者是图像中识别出的一般人物实体。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "WOMAN IN BLUE SUIT"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "PERSON"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "YOUNG BOY IN SUIT",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Young Boy in Suit是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'PERSON'相关联，后者是图像中识别出的一般人物实体。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "YOUNG BOY IN SUIT"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "PERSON"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "YOUNG GIRL IN BLUE COAT",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Young Girl in Blue Coat是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'PERSON'相关联，后者是图像中识别出的一般人物实体。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "YOUNG GIRL IN BLUE COAT"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "PERSON"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "MAN IN GRAY SUIT",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "Man in Gray Suit是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'PERSON'相关联，后者是图像中识别出的一般人物实体。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "MAN IN GRAY SUIT"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "PERSON"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "GROUP OF PEOPLE",
            "entity_type": "GROUP",
            "description": "Group of People是从image_1中提取的实体，可能与'DEFENDERS OF DEMOCRACY'相关联，后者是文本中提到的一个组织，两者都涉及人群的集合。",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "GROUP OF PEOPLE"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "DEFENDERS OF DEMOCRACY"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "image_2": [
        {
            "entity_name": "HIGHWAY INTERCHANGE",
            "entity_type": "GEO",
            "description": "A complex network of elevated roadways and bridges forming an interchange, with multiple levels and directions for vehicles to travel, as exemplified by Interstate 710 in Los Angeles which is known for its traffic congestion.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "HIGHWAY INTERCHANGE"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "INTERSTATE 710"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "VEHICLES",
            "entity_type": "OBJECT",
            "description": "Cars and trucks moving along the highways and ramps of the interchange, contributing to congestion and poor air quality, as observed on highways like Interstate 710.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "VEHICLES"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "INTERSTATE 710"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "PARKING LOT",
            "entity_type": "GEO",
            "description": "An area adjacent to the highway interchange with numerous parked cars, serving as a common feature near congested highways like Interstate 710.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "PARKING LOT"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "INTERSTATE 710"
            ]
        },
        {
            "entity_name": "BUILDINGS",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "Structures in the vicinity of the highway interchange, possibly commercial or residential, that can be affected by traffic and congestion as seen around Interstate 710.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "BUILDINGS"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "INTERSTATE 710"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "image_3": [
        {
            "entity_name": "December Jobs Report",
            "entity_type": "OBJECT",
            "description": "A bar chart displaying data on the monthly change in jobs, with a range from +200,000 to +600,000. The last bar, highlighted in red, indicates an increase of +223,000 jobs in December, as reported by the Labor Department. This data aligns with economists' expectations and reflects a slower but still comfortable rate of job creation at the end of 2022, suggesting the economy may be coming back into balance after years of pandemic-era disruptions.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "BAR CHART",
                "DECEMBER DATA"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "LABOR DEPARTMENT",
                "BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS",
                "S&P GLOBAL MARKET INTELLIGENCE",
                "FEDERAL RESERVE"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "image_4": [
        {
            "merged_entity_name": "NATIONAL A9-18",
            "entity_type": "EVENT",
            "description": "An event or section in a publication discussing severe weather impacts on California's trees, including heavy rain and broken trees.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "UPROOTED TREE"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "NATIONAL A9-18"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "image_5": [
        {
            "merged_entity_name": "City Ballet",
            "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
            "description": "A ballet company where Alexei Ratmansky joins as an artist in residence, featuring ballet dancers in various leotards performing different dance poses.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "DANCER 1",
                "DANCER 2",
                "DANCER 3",
                "DANCER 4"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "CITY BALLET"
            ]
        },
        {
            "merged_entity_name": "Alexei Ratmansky",
            "entity_type": "PERSON",
            "description": "A creative artist joining City Ballet as an artist in residence, allowing his imagination to run wild with the incorporation of various ballet dancers in his performances.",
            "source_image_entities": [
                "DANCER 1",
                "DANCER 2",
                "DANCER 3",
                "DANCER 4"
            ],
            "source_text_entities": [
                "ALEXEI RATMANSKY"
            ]
        }
    ]
}